# **LEVI JOHNSON**

(573) 355-2892 | lw.johnson.1227@gmail.com |Linkedin.com/in/levi-johnson-b35511204/

### **Education**

BS in Software Engineering | Brigham Young University - Idaho | Rexburg, Idaho

December 2024

• GPA 3.7 / 4.00

#### **Profile**

I am a highly motivated software engineering major with experience in various programming languages, complemented by a solid background in project management. My diverse skill set enables me to develop innovative software solutions while effectively coordinating and leading teams to successful outcomes.

# **Professional Experience**

Project Manager | Conservice LLC | Rexburg, Idaho

March 2023 - Present

Conservice provides utility and billing management to property owners and managers.

- Created a Project Hub for visibility with embedded HTML for project submissions.
- Developed an automatic email and chatbot for team updates using Google Apps Script.
- Developed and implemented Quality Control Sheets using Google Apps Script
- Overall Managed and completed 40+ projects.

Audit Analyst | Conservice LLC | Rexburg, Idaho

June 2021 - March 2023

Conservice provides utility and billing management to property owners and managers.

- Resolved billing mistakes saving clients over 150k dollars.
- Mastered systems of operation closing hundreds of issues per day.
- Communicated with clients in a professional and timely manner answering 20+ emails a day.

Deliveries Associate | Home Depot / Idaho Falls, Idaho

February 2021 - June 2021

Home Depot sells building materials and home products.

- Gained an understanding of Store layout helping customers to locate thousands of items.
- Organized and processed 25+ orders a day, insuring accurate delivery.
- Proficient at operating heavy-duty equipment such as forklift.

Mill Worker | Stair Sittings LLC / West Jordan, UT

April 2020 - December 2020

Stair fittings creates and sells stairs, sidings, and newels.

- Cut, glued, and sanded over a thousand feet of lumber for hundreds of orders.
- Trained multiple employees to run five different machines.
- Complied with precision to all of OSHA safety procedures.

# **Languages, Tools and Certifications**

Languages:

- Python, C#, JavaScript SQL, C, React, HTML/CSS, JSON, PowerShell Tools:
- Visual Studio Code, Google Sheets, Microsoft Excell, Cloud Databases, GitHub, Chrome DevTools, Figma Certifications:
- CompTIA Security +

## **Classes and Interests**

Completed Classes:

 Object Oriented Programming, Software Quality Assurance, Web Design and Development, User Interface Eval & Design, Software Lifecycle Models, Operating Systems Fundamentals, Networking, Intro to Cybersecurity, Applied Programming, Programming w/ Data Structures, Software Testing

#### Other Interests:

• Golf, Basketball, Weightlifting, Cold plunging